https://www.bullocks-safes.com/privacy.php

Skip to content
Phone:  (810) 736-7680 We are a Stocking Dealer for National Security and Liberty Safes with over 100 safes in stock.>>Financing is available through First Mutual Finance. <<Use Merchant ID: 1153We also buy used safes.
Independent Factory Authorized Liberty Safe Retailer
Toggle navigation
Gun Safes
Liberty Safes
National Safes
Fatboy Safes
Colt Safes
Specialty Safes
Which Safe is Right For You?
Special Offers
Request a Catalog
Services & Support...
The security of your personal information is very important to us. We never sell or rent your
personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We value your
trust very highly, and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal
information you provide to us and will only use it as we have described in our
Privacy Policy.
What Personal Information We Collect
We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using
the Libertysafe.com Web site. This information can include your name, street address,
and phone number when you order a Safe on the site. We may also ask for personal
information when you contact our Customer Service. This will allow us to protect
your confidentiality by verifying your identity.
Purchase Information
When you make order a safe we collect your name, your billing address and phone number.
We collect this information in order submit your order to an authorized Liberty
dealer close to you.
Cookies and Other Computer Information
When you order a safe at Liberty Safe.com you will be assigned a cookie (a small text
file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is
to identify you with your shopping basket.
How We Use Your Personal Information
Information we collect on Libertysafe.com may be used to enhance your shopping experience
in the following ways:
Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests
Communicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices
to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer
information only with our agents, representatives and trusted service providers
and contractors for limited purposes, including fulfilling customer orders; offering
certain products and services in connection with our Web site; communicating to
customers; providing customer service; enhancing and improving customers' shopping
experience; enabling access to our partners' sites; providing a personalized shopping
experience; and completing credit card transactions.
Aside
from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information
with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special
circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required
by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our
partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any
individual person.
More About Your Privacy
We realize that making purchases at Libertysafe.com, or any other Web site, requires
trust on your part. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you, our customer,
that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information
you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set
forth in this Policy. This includes your name, address, phone number, and/or email
address, credit-, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked
to you, personally.
We believe that you have a right to know, before shopping
at Libertysafe.com, or at any other time, exactly what information we might collect
from you, why we collect it and how we use it.
Changes to Liberty Safe’s Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. If we make
any significant change to this policy, we will post notice of the change on Libertysafe.com.
for a period of at least six months after the change is implemented.
Contacting Libertysafe.com
We will use your email address to respond to your questions, suggestions, and/or
requests for assistance in using our site. For questions or comments regarding
this policy, you may contact Liberty Safe and Security Products, Inc. at:
Email:
webmaster@libertysafe.com
Phone: 1-800-247-5625
Mail: Liberty Safe and Security Products, Inc.
1199 West Utah Avenue
Payson, UT 84651
